早上好  史蒂文斯波因特的观众朋友们
Good morning, Stevens point.
欢迎来到《尼比斯私房菜》
And welcome to “Nibblin' with Nimbus"
每一周  威斯康星周最受喜爱的气象学家
where every week, Wisconsin's favorite meteorologist...
也就是我  会给史蒂文斯波因特
this guy... cooks up some breakfast
最吸引人的住户或者游客做一顿早餐
for one of Stevens point's most intriguing residents or visitors.
而这周 除了美味的早餐
And this week, we got a tasty combination
我们还请到了
of breakfast brats
《放声歌唱》里的丽芙·鲁尼
and the always flavorful star
这个组合是不是会回味无穷呢
of “Sing Ot Loud," Liv Rooney.
我努力了整个晚上
I tried all night
来把我的狼耳朵和獠牙取下来
to get my ears and my fangs off.
它们固若金汤啊  我试着取消采访
They wouldn't budge. I tried cancelling
但是强尼·尼比斯还是准时出现了
and Johnny nimbus showed up anyway.
所以我做了任何好演员都会做的事
So I did what any great actress would do.
我把我歪瓜裂枣的地方都用戏服与道具藏好了
I hid my flaws with wardrobe and props.
现在出场的这位就是她了
Live and in person, here she is now.
哇  丽芙·鲁尼  这身行头不错啊
Wow, Liv Rooney, that is a nice getup.
告诉我  这几天孩子们都穿的像你一样么
Tell me, is that what all the kids are wearing these days?
若不是的话  看完节目他们就会了
'Cause if not, they will be after watching this.
啊  我在扯什么呢
Ah, who am I kidding?
我们的节目是没有孩子看的
No kids are watching this program.
强尼  你真是可爱啊
Johnny, you are adorable.
告诉我们  你今早要做什么呢
So tell us, what are you cooking up this morning?
好的  我会用平底锅来烤香肠
Well, I got a griddle full of brats
还要用与你加深了解做配菜
and a side order of get to know you.
哈
Huh?
很好 现在准备做水煎蛋了
Okay, now these eggs are ready for poaching.
这里分享一个从俺奶奶那儿学到的小窍门
And here's a secret I learned from Nana nimbus.
不要用水来煎  改用清鸡汤吧
Don't use water. Use chicken broth instead.
丽芙·鲁尼  你能帮我开一下么
Liv Rooney, could you open that for me.
- 好的  - 好极了
- Mm-hmm. - All right.
开好了 强尼
Here you go, Johnny.
哇 速度真快
Wow! That was quick.
很好  现在开始煎蛋了
All right. Now get poaching.
很不错
There you go.
就只要随意的把鸡汤倒进去
Just liberally putting it in there.
做好了就会非常美味的
They're gonna taste great.
很好 现在
Okay. Now.
来坐到桌前侃侃大山吧
Let's sit down to chew the fat.
照字面意思讲
And I mean that literally.
这些烤香肠九成都是脂肪
These brats are 90% fat.
快来吧 丽芙
Well, come on, Liv.
快来把你的牙深深地咬进
Come on over and sink your teeth
这些烤香肠里
into one of these babies.
我的亲娘啊
Oopsie-Daisy.
噢  丽芙  我来拉你起来
Oh, Liv, here. Let me help you up.
我的老天爷啊
Here... oh!
是我被咖啡灌糊涂了
Either I've had too much coffee,
还是狼人是真的
or werewolves are real!
呃
Um...
呃  没有啦  事实上  强尼
Uh, no. Actually, Johnny,
我只是给你们电视四台一个独家新闻
I am just giving you a channel four exclusive.
我将会成为《太空狼人》的主演
I am up for the lead in "space werewolves,"
所以为了让粉丝们小激动一下
so to get my fans excited,
我决定让你们先睹为快一下
I decided that I would give you a little sneak peek.
哦
Oh!
说实话
Seriously.
你差点把我吓尿了
You're kind of freaking me out.